Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public services records, 1968-2005; 1997-2005; Accession 2005-A-043
  - Subject correspondence [reference]
    - Manuscript collections [copies of reference correspondence relating to individual collections,], circa 1968-2000
      - MS 698 (Box 26, Folder 1211)
      - MS 701 (Box 26, Folder 1212)
      - MS 702 (Box 26, Folder 1213)
      - MS 704 (Box 26, Folder 1214)
      - MS 705 (Box 26, Folder 1215)
      - MS 706 (Box 26, Folder 1216)
      - MS 707 (Box 26, Folder 1217)
      - MS 708 (Box 26, Folder 1218)
      - MS 709 (Box 26, Folder 1219)
      - MS 711 (Box 26, Folder 1220)
      - MS 712 (Box 26, Folder 1221)
      - MS 713 (Box 26, Folder 1222)
      - MS 716 (Box 26, Folder 1223)
      - MS 719 (Box 26, Folder 1224)
      - MS 720 (Box 26, Folder 1225)
      - MS 721 (Box 26, Folder 1226)
      - MS 723 (Box 26, Folder 1227)
      - MS 725 (Box 26, Folder 1228)
      - MS 726 (Box 26, Folder 1229)
      - MS 727 (Box 26, Folder 1230)
      - MS 728 (Box 26, Folder 1231)
      - MS 729 (Box 26, Folder 1232)
      - MS 730 (Box 26, Folder 1233)
      - MS 734 (Box 26, Folder 1234)
      - MS 737 (Box 26, Folder 1235)
      - MS 739 (Box 26, Folder 1236)
      - MS 741 (Box 26, Folder 1237)
      - MS 742 (Box 26, Folder 1238)
      - MS 743 (Box 26, Folder 1239)
      - MS 745 (Box 26, Folder 1240)
      - MS 746 (Box 26, Folder 1241)
      - MS 749 (Box 26, Folder 1242)
      - MS 750 (Box 26, Folder 1243)
      - MS 753 (Box 26, Folder 1244)
      - MS 754 (Box 26, Folder 1245)
      - MS 755 (Box 26, Folder 1246)
      - MS 757 (Box 26, Folder 1247)
      - MS 759 (Box 26, Folder 1248)
      - MS 762 (Box 26, Folder 1249)
      - MS 765 (Box 26, Folder 1250)
      - MS 766 (Box 26, Folder 1251)
      - MS 768 (Box 26, Folder 1252)
      - MS 769 (Box 26, Folder 1253)
      - MS 770 (Box 26, Folder 1254)
      - MS 771 (Box 26, Folder 1255)
      - MS 773 (Box 26, Folder 1256)
      - MS 774 (Box 26, Folder 1257)
      - MS 775 (Box 26, Folder 1258)
      - MS 779 (Box 26, Folder 1259)
      - MS 781 (Box 26, Folder 1260)
      - MS 783 (Box 26, Folder 1261)
      - MS 787 (Box 26, Folder 1262)
      - MS 788 (Box 26, Folder 1263)
      - MS 789 (Box 26, Folder 1264)
      - MS 791 (Box 26, Folder 1265)
      - MS 794 (Box 26, Folder 1266)
      - MS 795 (Box 26, Folder 1267)
      - MS 797 (Box 26, Folder 1268)
      - MS 800 (Box 26, Folder 1269)
      - MS 801 (Box 26, Folder 1270)
      - MS 804 (Box 26, Folder 1271)
      - MS 806 (Box 26, Folder 1272)
      - MS 811 (Box 26, Folder 1273)
      - MS 814 (Box 26, Folder 1274)
      - MS 815 (Box 26, Folder 1275)
      - MS 816 (Box 26, Folder 1276)
      - MS 817 (Box 26, Folder 1277)
      - MS 820 (Box 26, Folder 1278)
      - MS 821 (Box 26, Folder 1279)
      - MS 822 (Box 26, Folder 1280)
      - MS 823 (Box 26, Folder 1281)
      - MS 824 (Box 26, Folder 1282)
      - MS 825 (Box 26, Folder 1283)
      - MS 826 (Box 26, Folder 1284)
      - MS 829 (Box 26, Folder 1285)
      - MS 830 (Box 26, Folder 1286)
      - MS 831 (Box 26, Folder 1287)
      - MS 835 (Box 26, Folder 1288)
      - MS 837 (Box 26, Folder 1289)
      - MS 840 (Box 26, Folder 1290)
      - MS 841 (Box 26, Folder 1291)
      - MS 842 (Box 26, Folder 1292)
      - MS 843 (Box 26, Folder 1293)
      - MS 844 (Box 26, Folder 1294)
      - MS 845 (Box 26, Folder 1295)
      - MS 846 (Box 26, Folder 1296)
      - MS 849 (Box 26, Folder 1297)
      - MS 850 (Box 26, Folder 1298)
      - MS 851 (Box 26, Folder 1299)
      - MS 854 (Box 26, Folder 1300)
      - MS 855 (Box 26, Folder 1301)
      - MS 857 (Box 26, Folder 1302)
      - MS 858 (Box 26, Folder 1303)
      - MS 859 (Box 26, Folder 1304)
      - MS 862 (Box 26, Folder 1305)
      - MS 863 (Box 26, Folder 1306)
      - MS 864 (Box 26, Folder 1307)
      - MS 867 (Box 26, Folder 1308)
      - MS 871 (Box 26, Folder 1309)
      - MS 874 (Box 26, Folder 1310)
      - MS 875 (Box 26, Folder 1311)
      - MS 876 (Box 26, Folder 1312)
      - MS 879 (Box 26, Folder 1313)
      - MS 882 (Box 26, Folder 1314)
      - MS 885 (Box 26, Folder 1315)
      - MS 889 (Box 26, Folder 1316)
      - MS 890 (Box 26, Folder 1317)
      - MS 891 (Box 26, Folder 1318)
      - MS 892 (Box 26, Folder 1319)
      - MS 893 (Box 26, Folder 1320)
      - MS 896 (Box 26, Folder 1321)
      - MS 897 (Box 26, Folder 1322)
      - MS 898 (Box 26, Folder 1323)
      - MS 900 (Box 26, Folder 1324)
      - MS 906 (Box 26, Folder 1325)
      - MS 908 (Box 26, Folder 1326)
      - MS 909 (Box 26, Folder 1327)
      - MS 912 (Box 26, Folder 1328)
      - MS 918 (Box 26, Folder 1329)
      - MS 921 (Box 26, Folder 1330)
      - MS 929 (Box 26, Folder 1331)
      - MS 937 (Box 26, Folder 1332)
      - MS 940 (Box 26, Folder 1333)
      - MS 946 (Box 26, Folder 1334)
      - MS 948 (Box 26, Folder 1335)
      - MS 957 (Box 26, Folder 1336)
      - MS 959 (Box 26, Folder 1337)
      - MS 961 (Box 26, Folder 1338)
      - MS 966 (Box 26, Folder 1339)
      - MS 968 (Box 26, Folder 1340)
      - MS 976 (Box 26, Folder 1341)
      - MS 978 (Box 26, Folder 1342)
      - MS 985 (Box 26, Folder 1343)
      - MS 986 (Box 26, Folder 1344)
      - MS 992 (Box 26, Folder 1345)
      - MS 999 (Box 26, Folder 1346)
      - MS 1005 (Box 26, Folder 1347)
      - MS 1009 (Box 26, Folder 1348)
      - MS 1010 (Box 26, Folder 1349)
      - MS 1013 (Box 26, Folder 1350)
      - MS 1017 (Box 26, Folder 1351)
      - MS 1020 (Box 26, Folder 1352)
      - MS 1022 (Box 26, Folder 1353)
      - MS 1024 (Box 26, Folder 1354)
      - MS 1026 (Box 26, Folder 1355)
      - MS 1030 (Box 26, Folder 1356)
      - MS 1031 (Box 26, Folder 1357)
      - MS 1034 (Box 26, Folder 1358)
      - MS 1037 (Box 26, Folder 1359)
      - MS 1038 (Box 26, Folder 1360)
      - MS 1039 (Box 26, Folder 1361)
      - MS 1042 (Box 26, Folder 1362)
      - MS 1043 (Box 26, Folder 1363)
      - MS 1044 (Box 26, Folder 1364)
      - MS 1046 (Box 26, Folder 1365)
      - MS 1051 (Box 26, Folder 1366)
      - MS 1055 (Box 26, Folder 1367)
      - MS 1061 (Box 27, Folder 1368)
      - MS 1067 (Box 27, Folder 1369)
      - MS 1070 (Box 27, Folder 1370)
      - MS 1072 (Box 27, Folder 1371)
      - MS 1077 (Box 27, Folder 1372)
      - MS 1083 (Box 27, Folder 1373)
      - MS 1087 (Box 27, Folder 1374)
      - MS 1089 (Box 27, Folder 1375)
      - MS 1090 (Box 27, Folder 1376)
      - MS 1091 (Box 27, Folder 1377)
      - MS 1093 (Box 27, Folder 1378)
      - MS 1094 (Box 27, Folder 1379)
      - MS 1095 (Box 27, Folder 1380)
      - MS 1097 (Box 27, Folder 1381)
      - MS 1099 (Box 27, Folder 1382)
      - MS 1101 (Box 27, Folder 1383)
      - MS 1107 (Box 27, Folder 1384)
      - MS 1108 (Box 27, Folder 1385)
      - MS 1110 (Box 27, Folder 1386)
      - MS 1111 (Box 27, Folder 1387)
      - MS 1113 (Box 27, Folder 1388)
      - MS 1119 (Box 27, Folder 1389)
      - MS 1122 (Box 27, Folder 1390)
      - MS 1129 (Box 27, Folder 1391)
      - MS 1131 (Box 27, Folder 1392)
      - MS 1132 (Box 27, Folder 1393)
      - MS 1133 (Box 27, Folder 1394)
      - MS 1136 (Box 27, Folder 1395)
      - MS 1138 (Box 27, Folder 1396)
      - MS 1139 (Box 27, Folder 1397)
      - MS 1140 (Box 27, Folder 1398)
      - MS 1143 (Box 27, Folder 1399)
      - MS 1144 (Box 27, Folder 1400)
      - MS 1145 (Box 27, Folder 1401)
      - MS 1146 (Box 27, Folder 1402)
      - MS 1149 (Box 27, Folder 1403)
      - MS 1154 (Box 27, Folder 1404)
      - MS 1156 (Box 27, Folder 1405)
      - MS 1167 (Box 27, Folder 1406)
      - MS 1168 (Box 27, Folder 1407)
      - MS 1171 (Box 27, Folder 1408)
      - MS 1176 (Box 27, Folder 1409)
      - MS 1181 (Box 27, Folder 1410)
      - MS 1184 (Box 27, Folder 1411)
      - MS 1189 (Box 27, Folder 1412)
      - MS 1192 (Box 27, Folder 1413)
      - MS 1198 (Box 27, Folder 1414)
      - MS 1200 (Box 27, Folder 1415)
      - MS 1201 (Box 27, Folder 1416)
      - MS 1204 (Box 27, Folder 1417)
      - MS 1206 (Box 27, Folder 1418)
      - MS 1210 (Box 27, Folder 1419)
      - MS 1212 (Box 27, Folder 1420)
      - MS 1218 (Box 27, Folder 1421)
      - MS 1231 (Box 27, Folder 1422)
      - MS 1232 (Box 27, Folder 1423)
      - MS 1233 (Box 27, Folder 1424)
      - MS 1235 (Box 27, Folder 1425)
      - MS 1236 (Box 27, Folder 1426)
      - MS 1239 (Box 27, Folder 1427)
      - MS 1241 (Box 27, Folder 1428)
      - MS 1245 (Box 27, Folder 1429)
      - MS 1247 (Box 27, Folder 1430)
      - MS 1248 (Box 27, Folder 1431)
      - MS 1255 (Box 27, Folder 1432)
      - MS 1258 (Box 27, Folder 1433)
      - MS 1259 (Box 27, Folder 1434)
      - MS 1262 (Box 27, Folder 1435)
      - MS 1267 (Box 27, Folder 1436)
      - MS 1271 (Box 27, Folder 1437)
      - MS 1272 (Box 27, Folder 1438)
      - MS 1279 (Box 27, Folder 1439)
      - MS 1280 (Box 27, Folder 1440)
      - MS 1281 (Box 27, Folder 1441)
      - MS 1283 (Box 27, Folder 1442)
      - MS 1284 (Box 27, Folder 1443)
      - MS 1287 (Box 27, Folder 1444)
      - MS 1291 (Box 27, Folder 1445)
      - MS 1294 (Box 27, Folder 1446)
      - MS 1295 (Box 27, Folder 1447)
      - MS 1296 (Box 27, Folder 1448)
      - MS 1297 (Box 27, Folder 1449)
      - MS 1302 (Box 27, Folder 1450)
      - MS 1303 (Box 27, Folder 1451)
      - MS 1308 (Box 27, Folder 1452)
      - MS 1311 (Box 27, Folder 1453)
      - MS 1312 (Box 27, Folder 1454)
      - MS 1315 (Box 27, Folder 1455)
      - MS 1316 (Box 27, Folder 1456)
      - MS 1317 (Box 27, Folder 1457)
      - MS 1318 (Box 27, Folder 1458)
      - MS 1319 (Box 27, Folder 1459)
      - MS 1320 (Box 27, Folder 1460)
      - MS 1321 (Box 27, Folder 1461)
      - MS 1326 (Box 27, Folder 1462)
      - MS 1331 (Box 27, Folder 1463)
      - MS 1333 (Box 27, Folder 1464)
      - MS 1334 (Box 27, Folder 1465)
      - MS 1338 (Box 27, Folder 1466)
      - MS 1341 (Box 27, Folder 1467)
      - MS 1343 (Box 27, Folder 1468)
      - MS 1344 (Box 27, Folder 1469)
      - MS 1345 (Box 27, Folder 1470)
      - MS 1348 (Box 27, Folder 1471)
      - MS 1349 (Box 27, Folder 1472)
      - MS 1350 (Box 27, Folder 1473)
      - MS 1351 (Box 27, Folder 1474)
      - MS 1352 (Box 27, Folder 1475)
      - MS 1353 (Box 27, Folder 1476)
      - MS 1356 (Box 27, Folder 1477)
      - MS 1357 (Box 27, Folder 1478)
      - MS 1359 (Box 27, Folder 1479)
      - MS 1361 (Box 27, Folder 1480)
      - MS 1363 (Box 27, Folder 1481)
      - MS 1366 (Box 27, Folder 1482)
      - MS 1367 (Box 27, Folder 1483)
      - MS 1369 (Box 27, Folder 1484)
      - MS 1370 (Box 27, Folder 1485)
      - MS 1371 (Box 27, Folder 1486)
      - MS 1372 (Box 27, Folder 1487)
      - MS 1373 (Box 27, Folder 1488)
      - MS 1375 (Box 27, Folder 1489)
      - MS 1380 (Box 27, Folder 1490)
      - MS 1387 (Box 27, Folder 1491)
      - MS 1388 (Box 27, Folder 1492)
      - MS 1389 (Box 27, Folder 1493)
      - MS 1391 (Box 27, Folder 1494)
      - MS 1393 (Box 27, Folder 1495)
      - MS 1395 (Box 27, Folder 1496)
      - MS 1398 (Box 27, Folder 1497)
      - MS 1399 (Box 27, Folder 1498)
      - MS 1406 (Box 27, Folder 1499)
      - MS 1410 (Box 27, Folder 1500)
      - MS 1411 (Box 27, Folder 1501)
      - MS 1418 (Box 27, Folder 1502)
      - MS 1419 (Box 27, Folder 1503)
      - MS 1421 (Box 27, Folder 1504)
      - MS 1428 (Box 27, Folder 1505)
      - MS 1430 (Box 27, Folder 1506)
      - MS 1432 (Box 27, Folder 1507)
      - MS 1436 (Box 27, Folder 1508)
      - MS 1439 (Box 27, Folder 1509)
      - MS 1440 (Box 27, Folder 1510)
      - MS 1443 (Box 27, Folder 1511)
      - MS 1446 (Box 27, Folder 1512)
      - MS 1447 (Box 27, Folder 1513)
      - MS 1449 (Box 27, Folder 1514)
      - MS 1452 (Box 27, Folder 1515)
      - MS 1453 (Box 27, Folder 1516)
      - MS 1454 (Box 27, Folder 1517)
      - MS 1455 (Box 27, Folder 1518)
      - MS 1456 (Box 27, Folder 1519)
      - MS 1458 (Box 27, Folder 1520)
      - MS 1460 (Box 27, Folder 1521)
      - MS 1461 (Box 27, Folder 1522)
      - MS 1464 (Box 27, Folder 1523)
      - MS 1465 (Box 27, Folder 1524)
      - MS 1472 (Box 27, Folder 1525)
      - MS 1474 (Box 27, Folder 1526)
      - MS 1475 (Box 27, Folder 1527)
      - MS 1478 (Box 27, Folder 1528)
      - MS 1483 (Box 27, Folder 1529)
      - MS 1487 (Box 27, Folder 1530)
      - MS 1488 (Box 27, Folder 1531)
      - MS 1489 (Box 27, Folder 1532)
      - MS 1492 (Box 27, Folder 1533)
      - MS 1494 (Box 27, Folder 1534)
      - MS 1495 (Box 27, Folder 1535)
      - MS 1498 (Box 27, Folder 1536)
      - MS 1499 (Box 27, Folder 1537)
      - MS 1500 (Box 27, Folder 1538)
      - MS 1556 (Box 27, Folder 1539)
      - MS 1559 (Box 27, Folder 1540)
      - MS 1567 (Box 27, Folder 1541)
      - MS 1575 (Box 27, Folder 1542)
      - MS 1580 (Box 27, Folder 1543)
      - MS 1584 (Box 27, Folder 1544)
      - MS 1590 (Box 27, Folder 1545)
      - MS 1591 (Box 27, Folder 1546)
      - MS 1594 (Box 27, Folder 1547)
      - MS 1595 (Box 27, Folder 1548)
      - MS 1596 (Box 27, Folder 1549)
      - MS 1601 (Box 27, Folder 1550)
      - MS 1602 (Box 27, Folder 1551)
      - MS 1603 (Box 27, Folder 1552)
      - MS 1604 (Box 27, Folder 1553)
      - MS 1607 (Box 27, Folder 1554)
      - MS 1611 (Box 27, Folder 1555)
      - MS 1614 (Box 27, Folder 1556)
      - MS 1617 (Box 27, Folder 1557)
      - MS 1618 (Box 27, Folder 1558)
      - MS 1619 (Box 27, Folder 1559)
      - MS 1622 (Box 27, Folder 1560)
      - MS 1625 (Box 27, Folder 1561)
      - MS 1641 (Box 27, Folder 1562)
      - MS 1647 (Box 27, Folder 1563)
      - MS 1652 (Box 27, Folder 1564)
      - MS 1659 (Box 27, Folder 1565)
      - MS 1660 (Box 27, Folder 1566)
      - MS 1664 (Box 27, Folder 1567)
      - MS 1665 (Box 27, Folder 1568)
      - MS 1666 (Box 27, Folder 1569)
      - MS 1670 (Box 27, Folder 1570)
      - MS 1676 (Box 27, Folder 1571)
      - MS 1682 (Box 27, Folder 1572)
      - MS 1685 (Box 27, Folder 1573)
      - MS 1688 (Box 27, Folder 1574)
      - MS 1690 (Box 27, Folder 1575)
      - MS 1691 (Box 27, Folder 1576)
      - MS 1695 (Box 27, Folder 1577)
      - MS 1700 (Box 27, Folder 1578)
      - MS 1703 (Box 27, Folder 1579)
      - MS 1706 (Box 27, Folder 1580)
      - MS 1710 (Box 27, Folder 1581)
      - MS 1720 (Box 27, Folder 1582)
      - MS 1725 (Box 27, Folder 1583)
      - MS 1728 (Box 27, Folder 1584)
      - MS 1729 (Box 27, Folder 1585)
      - MS 1734 (Box 27, Folder 1586)
      - MS 1738 (Box 27, Folder 1587)
      - MS 1742 (Box 27, Folder 1588)
      - MS 1743 (Box 27, Folder 1589)
      - MS 1745 (Box 27, Folder 1590)
      - MS 1746 (Box 27, Folder 1591)
      - MS 1780 (Box 27, Folder 1592)
      - MS 1783 (Box 27, Folder 1593)
    - Thank you letters, 1991-2005 (Box 28, Folder 1594 - 1603)
  - Registration and application to examine cards [in-person] [arranged chronologically by fiscal year, then alphabetically by surname]
    - FY 1998 A -R, 1997-1998 (Box 29)
    - FY 1998 S -Z, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - FY 1999 A -L, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - FY 1999 M -Z, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - FY 2000 A -Gl, 1999-2000 (Box 31)
    - FY 2000 Go -Z, 1999-2000 (Box 32)
    - FY 2001 A -Ch, 2000-2001 (Box 32)
    - FY 2001 Cl -V, 2000-2001 (Box 33)
    - FY 2001 W -Z, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
    - FY 2002 A -S, 2001-2002 (Box 34)
    - FY 2002 T -Z, 2001-2002 (Box 35)
    - FY 2003 A -R, 2002-2003 (Box 35)
    - FY 2003 S -Z, 2002-2003 (Box 36)
    - FY 2004 A -M, 2003-2004 (Box 36)
    - FY 2004 N -Z, 2003-2004 (Box 37)
  - Call slips [through 1999-2000 arranged alphabetically by patron surname within category; from 2000-2001 on arranged by number within category (RU # for archives)]
    - Archives -patrons, 1998-1999 (Box 38)
    - Microfilms -patrons, 1998-1999 (Box 38)
    - Publications -patrons, 1998-1999 (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts -patrons, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Archives -staff, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Microfilms -staff, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Publications -staff, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Manuscripts -staff, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Manuscripts -patrons, 1999-2000 (Box 40)
    - Manuscripts -staff, 1999-2000 (Box 40)
    - Video Archives -patrons, 1999-2000 (Box 40)
    - Video Archives -staff, 1999-2000 (Box 40)
    - Microfilms -patrons, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Publications -patrons, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Archives -patrons, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Microfilms -staff, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Publications -staff, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Archives -staff, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Archives, 2000-2001 (Box 42)
    - Publications, 2000-2001 (Box 42)
    - Manuscripts, 2000-2001 (Box 43)
    - Microfilms, 2000-2001 (Box 43)
    - Manuscripts, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
    - Microfilms, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
    - Publications, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
    - Archives, 2001-2002 (Box 45)
    - All call slips FY 2003 Jul -Nov [arranged by month cleared, then by collection number], 2002 (Box 45)
    - All call slips FY 2003 Dec -Jun arranged by month cleared, then by collection number], 2002-2003 (Box 46)
    - All call slips FY 2004 Jul -Feb [arranged by month cleared, then by collection number], 2003-2004 (Box 47)
    - All call slips FY 2004 Mar -Jun [arranged by month cleared, then by collection number] (Box 48)
    - All call slips FY 2005 Jul -Nov [arranged by month cleared, then by collection number], 2004 (Box 48)
    - All call slips FY 2005 Dec -Jun [May missing] [arranged by month cleared, then by collection number], 2004-2005 (Box 49)
  - Reprographics Orders Log Book, 1998-1999 (Box 50, Folder 1604)
  - Canceled reprographics orders not interfiled in reference correspondence [arranged by fiscal year, then by patron surname] (Box 50)
    - FY 2000 A -W, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 1605)
    - FY 2001 A -F, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 1606)
    - FY 2001 G -L, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 1607)
    - FY 2001 M -W, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 1608)
  - Photography Request Forms FY2003-FY2005, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 1609 - 1611)
  - Richard C. Lee Papers access agreements (illegible signatures), 2000 (Box 51, Folder 1612)
- Public Services records, 2005-2006; Accession 2008-A-016
  - Reference Correspondence
    - AA-ALV, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AM-AZ, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - BA-BAR, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BAS-BAN, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BER-BIS, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BLA-BOY, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BRA-BRY, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BU-BUT, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - CA-CAR, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - CAS-CHU, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CLA-COO, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - COP-CUT, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - DAH-DEM, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - DEN-DON, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - DOS-DZ, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - E, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - FAB-FIT, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - FLE-FUR, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - GAB-GER, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - GHE-GOU, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - GRA-GWL, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - HAC-HAM, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - HAN-HAY, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - HEA-HER, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - HOC-HON, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - HOP-HUT, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - IBR-JAS, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - JEA-JUB, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - KAB-KIS, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - KLA-KOP, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - KOV-KWA, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - LAA-LEM, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - LEO-LIN, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - LIS-LYO, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - MAC-MAZ, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - McC-McS, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - MEA-MIC, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - MIL-MON, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - MOO-MUT, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - N, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - O, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - PAC-PEP, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - PER-POP, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - POV-QUI, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - RAA-RIS, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - ROB-ROH, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - ROS-RYA, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - SAB-SAW, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - SCA-SCO, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - SEA-SIN, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - SIR-SON, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - SOO-STI, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - STO-SZA, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - TAB-THO, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - TID-TY, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - U-V, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - WAD-WAR, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - WAS-WES, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - WEW-WIL, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - WIN-WYN, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - X-Z, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - "Thank You", 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Completed Copy Orders
    - A-Bh, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Br-Cq, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Cr-E, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - F-G, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - H, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - J-Keq, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Ker-Ki, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Ko-Ku, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - L-La, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Le-Li, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Lo-Ly, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - M-Mi, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Mo-Mu, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - N, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - O, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - P, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Q, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - R, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - S, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - T, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - U-V, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - W-Z, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Application to Publish Facsimile Reproduction, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Authorization to Publish, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Application to Examine
    - A-K, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - L-Z, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Completed Office of Origin Requests
    - YRG 1-12, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - YRG 13-20, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - YRG 21-27, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - YRG 28-46, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Sign In Register Sheets, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 93 - 94)
  - Call Slips
    - Microform/Book/Yale Archives/Manuscript Collections, 2005-2006 (Box 6)
    - Manuscript Collections, 2005-2006 (Box 7)
- Public Services records, 2006-2008; Accession 2009-A-068
  - Correspondence
    - A - Am, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - An - Az, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - b- Baz, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Be - Bez, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bf - Bol, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bom - Bre, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Brf - Bz, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - C - Caz, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Cb- Cl, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Cm - Coo, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Cop - Cz, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - D - Dep, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Deq - Dor, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Dos - Dz, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - E - Ez, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - f- Fox, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Fp - Gi, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Gj - Go, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Gp - Ha, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - He - Hz, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - I - Jz, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - K - Kz, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - L - Li, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Lj - Mc, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Md - Mof, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Moh - Mz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - N - Oz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - p - Pz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Q - Rz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - S - Sh, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Si - Sz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - T - Tz, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 32)